maxforexonline.biz 2010-06-14

# Welcome to MaxForex Online

## Privacy Policy

## **At Privacy Policy :-**

## At Max Forex, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use the information and services provided by our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the products and services that are available on [www.maxforexonline.com](http://www.maxforexonline.com/)

## **Information Collection and Use**

## Max Forex is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Max Forex collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

## **Sharing and Usage**

## We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). The contracts prohibit them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may also disclose information to partners who introduced you to Max Forex 's services in order to ensure they are properly compensated for their efforts. Lastly, we may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

## **Use of Web Technologies**

## We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are the Use of Cookies: Cookies are minute files containing information that web sites use to track visitors. Via the Internet, Max Forex may access cookies on your computer. This process informs us on which websites, banners and advertisements bring users to our website. The usage of cookies does not affect a user's right to privacy in any way. Cookies allow us to verify the login status of customers using the service linked directly with our website, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our member signup program. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, enabling us to make your visit to our websites easier by recognizing you when you return and helping to provide you with a customized experience. We keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you. 

## **Links to other Sites**

## Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as our payment processor. While on these sites, Max Forex or its partners may collect information about you. Because Max Forex does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

## **Security**

## We have taken utmost care to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. This technology protects the user from having his information intercepted by third parties while transmitted to Max Forex. Max Forex takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

## **Notification of Changes**

## If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Website. So, you are requested to keep yourself updated by checking in with our Privacy policy from time to time, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use the information and services provided by our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the products and services that are available on www. Maxforexonline.com 

## **Information Collection and Use**

## Max Forex is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Max Forex collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

## **Sharing and Usage**

## We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). The contracts prohibit them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may also disclose information to partners who introduced you to Max Forex 's services in order to ensure they are properly compensated for their efforts. Lastly, we may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

##
